

Kanwal Saeed

Full Stack Developer | Accountant

0323-2194485 kanwalchuhan122@gmail.com www.kanwalsaeed.thespabank.com Nazimabad no-2 Karachi - Pakisan.

ABOUT ME

Your informed that,I'm Kanwal I've some experience my first experience has as a teacher in Radiant Public school and my second experience has as a Sales Executive in Maritime shipping International, after that I move on at Soneri Bank Limited. and I have also experience as a Office Assistant at Eastern Enterprises. To join a highly esteemed bank, which offers career growth in an excellent working environment, where I can flourish my abilities. I look forward receive an encouraging response soon.

CERTIFICATE OF ACHIEVEMEN

Certificate of

Web Designing And Engineering Institute Of Business Admissions (IBA) Government of Pakistan NAVTTC Karachi, Sindh, Pakistan. 2020 - 2021

Certificate of Service Transformation Transformers Karachi, Sindh, Pakistan. Dec 2013

Certificate of Trainee Cash Officer Program 2012 Soneri Bank Limited Karachi, Sindh, Pakistan. Jul 2012

LANGUAGES

English Urdu Punjabi

WORK HISTORY

Freelancer

<u>Fiverr and Upwork Freelancers (Buyers and Sellers)</u>

Nov 2017 - Present Full Stack Developer. Accountant Content Writing

Office Account Executive

Eastern Enterprises

Nov 2016 - Mar 2017

Responsible for all sales activities in the area, from lead generation to closing. Works closely with sales and support teams to foster high customer satisfaction and generate profit. Prepare Petty Cash, Organise all files, Prepare documents and emails, Conduct research work, Handle Letter of credit matters, with customers, suppliers and their banks, Bank and vendor Reconciliation.

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Teller Cash Officer

Soneri Bank Limited

Jul 2012 - Mar 2014 Karachi, Sindh, Pakistan.

Sales Executive

Maritime Shipping International

Jul 2009 - Mar 2010 Karachi, Sindh, Pakistan.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Karachi University

Bachelor's Degree in Commerce, B.Com Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan 2013

Institute Of Business Admissions (IBA)
Government of Pakistan NAVTTC
Web Designing And Engineering
Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan
2013

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- Core Php
- Mysql
- Laravel
- HTML CSS
- Bootstrap
- Java Script
- JQuery
- WordPress
- Word
- Power Point
- Excel
- Adobe Photoshop
- · Book Keeping
- Account Handler
- Petty Cash Management
- Bank Reconciliation
- Credior Reconcilation

REFERENCE

Will be made avaible on request.

Kanwal Saeed

Full Stack Developer | Accountant 0323-2194485 kanwalchuhan122@gmail.com www.kanwalsaeed.thespabank.com Nazimabad no-2 Karachi - Pakisan.